等一下 让爸爸…
Hold on, let me...
二零零八年四月十三日
- 让爸爸…  - 马掉下来了
Let me just...I dropped the horse.
等一下
Hold on.
好了 看看
There. Look.
塔哒! 看
Ta-da! See?
坏掉了吗?
Is it broken?
没有 看看 爸爸修好了 不 等等
No, look. Daddy fixed it. No, wait.
如果你先说我们在哪里 爸爸就给你
I'll give it to you when you tell me where we are first.
- 爸爸的爸爸家  - 对了
Dad's dad's house. That's right.
这是爷爷家
This was Grandpa's house.
你要相机吗?
Here, you want the camera?
拿着
Here, take it.
不 哎唷!
No. Owie!
不 带我去游戏房
No, no, no, show me the playroom.
等等 给我看看你的玩具
Wait, show your toys.
哦 没事 凯撒
Oh, it's okay, Caesar.
看来小凯撒乘车到有点累坏了 不是吗 伙伴?
I think Little Caesar's tired out from the drive.
詹姆斯? 为什么楼上没有窗帘?
- Aren't you, buddy? - James? Why aren't there any curtains upstairs?
因为我们在荒郊野外 没有人看见
Because, babe, we're in the middle of nowhere and no one's watching.
说声嗨 妈妈
Say hi, Mommy.
嗨 小甲虫
Hi, Junebug.
等等 我以为这个坏掉了
Wait a minute, I thought this was broken.
不 宝贝 小心点 妈妈不要让它再次弄坏
No, baby, please be careful. I just don't want it to break again.
- 爸爸修理  - 是
Daddy fixed it.Yeah.
我们要确定别让它再次坏掉
We just wanna make sure that we don't break it again.
那么 爸爸会再次修理 对吗?
Well, then I'm just gonna fix it again, aren't I?
那是什么?
What's that?
- 詹姆斯  - 海拔的缘故 我没事
- James. - It's just the altitude. I'm fine.
为什么爸爸的鼻子流血?
Why is your nose bleeding?
- 爸爸没事  - 你没事吧?
- Daddy's fine. - Are you okay?
修剪视频
最后一次家庭旅行
删除谷歌账号
删除我的账号
脑瘤类型 脑瘤护理
脑膜瘤- 原因 间变性脑膜瘤- 存活率
詹姆斯健康检查
帮助你的孩子疗伤
听说了你的消息
I just heard the news.
我无法想象你得经历的一切
Um, I can't imagine what you must be going through.
我们真的不想你离开 但我明白 你需要新的开始
We really hate to see you go, but I get it. You need a fresh start.
我真的不知道你所经历的一切
I had no idea what you were going through.
洛杉矶 加州 我感到很抱歉
Anyway, I'm just-- I'm so sorry.
打电话或者传信息 什么都好
Call or text, or whatever works.
我知道你现在得面对很多事情
I know you are dealing with a lot right now.
我们会想念你的
Just-- We're gonna miss you a lot.
但你们俩会挺过去的
But you two are gonna get through this.
给琼
我与你同在 有一天她会明白的
I'm here for you. Someday she'll understand.
警戒线不能越过
今早可怕的事态发展 绿色丰田佳美…
Frightening developments this morning as a green Toyota Camry--
搜救队伍继续寻找 但是目前尚不清楚…
A recovery operation is currently underway, but it's unclear--
今天令人震惊的发展 属于金女士的车
A shocking development today, as a vehicle belonging to Ms. Kim
被发现弃于海湾区湖之中 首席警探…
was found dumped in a Bay Area lake. The lead detective--
在这里
Here.
…玛戈特爸爸 大卫·金
…Margot's father, David Kim.
他们在湖边找到金女士钥匙扣
They found Ms. Kim's keychain near the lake this morning.
《非虚构》第三集 失踪的玛戈特·金
《非虚构》内的事实与虚构
《非虚构》 大卫·金 大卫·金现实生活
罗斯玛丽·维克警探
维纳死党 喂
琼?
不好意思 怎么了?
你拿到了吗?
还没有
我们现在需要钱
要不然 我的哥哥买不到…
我去拿 得流畅点 大声笑
她可能随时会打来
妈妈 Facetime
她现在打来了
文莫支付给我
接受
Siri 拨电话给琼
Hello--?Siri, call June.
- 天啊  - 妈妈?
Oh, my gosh.Mom?
Siri 请拨电话给小甲虫
Siri, please call Junebug.
妈妈 你在线上了 这是 Facetime
Mom, you're already on the phone. This is FaceTime.
天啊 你可以帮帮忙清除你的语音信箱?
Oh, gosh. Can you please do me a favor and clear your voicemail?
妈妈试着留言给你
I've been trying to leave you messages.
嗯 可能全都是妈妈的
Well, they're probably all from you.
妈妈不必用 Siri来做任何事情的 对吗?
You know you don't have to use Siri for literally everything, right?
听着 妈妈迟到了 我要你写下几件事
Listen, I am running late and I need you to write a couple of things down.
车钥匙放在厨房最上面的抽屉 凯文…
The car keys are gonna be in the top drawer in the kitchen, and Kevin--
妈妈叫你写下来 你没有写
I just said write it down. You're not writing it down.
便利贴
凯文转发了旅程给你
Kevin forwarded you the itinerary.
不可以喝酒 别打开门让陌生人进来
No alcohol, do not open the door for strangers.
然后开启定位服务…
And keep your location service turned on
天啊 闭嘴 …妈妈不在的这段时间 明白吗?
the entire time I'm away, do you understand?
别开玩笑 明白
No fun. Got it.
那么 食物等等的可以吗?
Uh, what about for like, you know, food or whatever?
我的钥匙放在希思那儿 需要的话联络她
I left a key with Heather. Call her if you need anything.What?
- 不 妈妈 我不需要希思  - 什么意思 「不」?
No. Mom, I don't need Heather.What do you mean, "No"?
我十八岁了 我不需要保姆
I am 18. I don't need a babysitter.
我不管你是不是十八岁 好吗?
I don't care if you're 18, okay?
那么多人之中你选了希思?
So you pick Heather, of all people?
你根本不明白妈妈所做的牺牲 来换取你要的生活
You do not understand the sacrifices I made to give you the life you have.
妈妈 你太夸张了
Mom, you're being so dramatic.
- 小甲虫 如果你能…  - 别再这样叫我!
Junebug, if you'd-- Stop calling me that!
妈妈只想要确定我不在的时候你安全
I just-- I just need to know that you're safe when I'm away.
好吧 凯文随时会联系优步
All right, Kevin's gonna be there any minute to call the Uber.
妈妈也存入一点钱在你的账户以备不时之需
I also just deposited some money into your account for emergencies.
明白吗?
Understand?
钱用来干嘛?
What's the money for?
以备不时之需
Emergencies.
格蕾丝·艾伦付$350
文莫 这是用来干嘛?
- 你收到了吗?  - 是 现在就去商店
You get it? Yep. Heading into the store now.
再见!
Bye!
敲敲门
Knock, knock.
那只猫就是不肯来
That cat just won't come around.
那部旧电脑怎么样?
How's the old computer running?
哦 是的 比较快了 谢谢
Oh, yeah. It's a little faster. Thanks.
没问题 伙伴
No problem, parcera.
什么?
What?
这是哥伦比亚的特色
Uh... It's a Colombian thing.
我正在学习西班牙语
I'm working on my Spanish.
酷
Cool.
我在商店里 要买什么?
嘿 我知道你享受放暑假的心情 但是…
Hey, um, I know you're in summer vacay mode, but, uh,
你有一点点时间吗?
you have a sec?
便宜的就行
我该怎么说呢?
How do I say this?
听着
Look.
我知道我只是
I know that I'm just
你刚认识的人
I don't know, the new guy to you.
但是我爱你的妈妈
But I love your mom.
我知道我计划了我和她的行程 但是…
And I know I planned this for just me and her
这是为了一个特别的原因
but it's for a very special reason.
- 凯?  - 那么 我们还未…
Kev?So before we--
- 嘿  - 嘿
Hey.Hey.
发生什么事?
What's goin' on?
我和琼正在聊着
June and I were just chatting.
好的 你联络优步了吗?
Oh, okay. Did you call the Uber?
两分钟车程 什么?
Two minutes away. What?
要拿行李下去吗?
Do you wanna take the bags down?
开车需要30秒…
It takes 30 seconds to wheel--
我知道 但我要谈谈…
I know, but I wanna talk...
好的 好吧 我外面等你
Okay, all right, I'll see you out there.
谢谢
Thank you.
当接我的女朋友 我这样做
欢迎从戒毒所回来!
真的吗?
Really?
听着 我很抱歉 如果我对你太严厉了
Look, I'm sorry if it seems like I'm hard on you.
但我只想确定你安全
But it really is just to make sure you're safe.
优步到了!
Uber's actually here!
好的 来着!
Okay, coming!
琼 听我说
June, listen to me.
你星期一到洛杉矶国际机场接我们 你做得到吗?
I need you to pick us up on Monday at LAX. Can you do that?
可以 妈妈
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
格蕾丝 听到吗?
Grace, you hear me?
铃声 前门动作感应
清除你的语音信箱好让我留言!
你下个星期可以来接我们吗?
我们在二十日中午抵达
等等 父亲节你不在?
妈妈已经告诉过你了 可以吗?
你不能更换机票吗?
妈妈试着打电话给你 琼 我们能谈谈吗?
清除你的语音信箱好让我留言!
妈妈爱你
回复
你准备好了…?
我们走吧
谜踪搜救
星期六 六月十一日
小睡
抵达哥伦比亚!
我是妈妈 短信发不过去
别作!
她走了!
维纳 接受
这个星期会是传奇
This week's gonna be legendary.
我快到了
Pulling up now.
酷 马上到
Cool. Be right there.
- 等等 维 她在这里!  - 谁?
- Wait, Vee, she's here! - Who?
希思 我妈妈的朋友
Heather. My mom's friend.
讨厌!
Shit!
嘿 琼
Hey, Junie.
不确定你在家 我带来了你的晚餐
Wasn't sure you'd be home. I brought some dinner for ya.
哦 放松 你好吗?
Oh, relax. How's it hangin'?
如何举办狂野的派对
哦 很好
Oh, it's-it's fine.
工作如何呢?
Um... How was work?
很好 我帮一个客户 打赢了监护权官司 那很好
It was good. I won a custody case for a client, so that's good.
我打赌你妈妈开始想念你了
Uh... I bet your mom already misses you.
凯文发送他们在沙滩上的照片 他最近一直在锻炼
You know, Kevin sent me a picture of them from the beach. He's been working out.
等等 凯文发送照片给你?
Wait, Kevin's sending you pictures?
很欣慰她找到了另一半
I'm just glad she found someone.
他很好 很可爱 很酷的技术工作
Someone nice and cute, cool tech job.
对不起 给我五分钟
那样的男人会迷死我 很难找到合适的男人
I'd kill for a guy like that. It's pretty rough out there.
不是说我没有乐趣 你明白吗?
Not that I don't have my fun. You know what I'm saying?
很不幸
Unfortunately.
一切都好吗?
Is everything okay?
她看到了酒?
哦 是的 没事 派对
Oh, yeah, yeah. It's fine.
如果你闷的话 我可以留下来陪你
You know, I could stay and hang if you're bored.
不 没事 我只是想在家里过个安静的夜晚
No, it's okay. I'm just looking forward to a quiet night in.
你好像你的妈妈
You're just like your mom.
不要发送那个帖子
Don't post that.
干杯 发送
星期日 六月十三日
林凯文 附件:一个图像
性感女友!
维纳向你发起收款$52.97
继续!
林凯文 附件:一个图像
和宝贝喝鸡尾酒
无酒精鸡尾酒
父亲节
嘿 今晚做好准备了吗?
Hey, you ready for tonight?
世上只有爸爸好!
是吧
I guess.
父亲节
你没事吧?
You, uh-- You doing okay?
祝我的头号舞伴父亲节快乐 爱你爸爸!
是的
Yeah.
是的 我没事
Yeah, I'm- I'm fine.
九点琼家集合!
铃声
- 哇塞 琼  - 我没事
Whoa, June.I'm fine.
- 冷静 坐下  - 我没事!
Calm down. Sit down.I'm fine!
琼 你没事吧?
Yo, June, you okay?
有没有人看到我的智能手表? 四方形还有…
Anybody seen my smartwatch? It's square with--
好的 没事 听我说
Okay. It's all right. All right, listen to me.
你没事 蒂亚 可以拿杯子吗?
You're all right. Tia, can you get the cup?
- 好的 我们走吧 别再喝了  - 抱歉
All right, let's go. You're done.I'm sorry.
没事 琼 没事
Okay, June, okay.
看来小凯撒乘车到有点累坏了
Aw, I think Little Caesar's tired out from the drive.
- 不是吗 伙伴?  - 詹姆斯? 为什么楼上没有窗帘?
- Aren't you, buddy? - James? Why aren't there any curtains upstairs?
因为我们在荒郊野外 没有人看见
Because, babe, we're in the middle of nowhere and no one's watching.
嗨 小甲虫
Hi, Junebug.
等等 我以为这个坏掉了
Wait a minute, I thought this was broken.
不 宝贝 小心点 妈妈不要让它再次弄坏
No, baby, please be careful. I just don't want it to break again.
- 爸爸修理  - 是
Daddy fixed it.Yeah.
我们要确定别让它再次坏掉
We just wanna make sure that we don't break it again.
那么 爸爸会再次修理
Well, then I'm just gonna fix it again.
但愿爸爸在这里
星期一 六月二十日
停
可能是叫这个名: 安杰尔
我是安杰尔…
如果你见到我的手表了麻烦告诉我一声
别在意昨天吐了一地 哈哈哈
去洛杉矶国际机场 接妈妈和凯文 今早十一点
天啊
Oh, shit.
维纳 琼没事吧?
嘿 你得空吗?
幸好你还活着!
不 我在工作
宿醉 我很不好
跑腿兔
你需要的时候帮助你 触手可及
做家务
钥匙在地垫下面 别偷东西
哈哈
聘用
录影
欢迎出狱 老妈!
嗨 我是格蕾丝·艾伦 请留言
Hi, this is Grace Allen. Please leave a message.
妈妈?
Mom?
喂?
你们在哪里呢? 我在这里等很久了
Where are you guys? I've been standing here forever.
你知道我在等着 对吧?
你收到了信息让我知道
Let me know when you get this.
妈妈你飞机落地了吗?
待会儿见 拜拜
See you in a sec. Bye.
Facetime
妈妈  Facetime 无法使用
洛杉矶国际机场 抵达
预订酒店
波马罗莎酒店 电话
嗨 我要询问你的旅客
Hi. I'm calling about a guest you had
想知道他们有没有延长逗留时间
seeing if they extended their stay.
在外面见
对不起 有没有会说英语的人?
I'm sorry. Does anyone speak English?
不 对不起
No, I'm sorry.
我就知道我不该放弃西班牙语
Knew I shouldn't have dropped Spanish. Um...
「能查一下房间预定吗」用西语怎么说
是林 拼作L- I...
Um... It's Lin. It's spelled L- I--
是 林凯文
Oh,s , Kevin Lin. Uh-huh.
是 就是他
Yeah. That's him. Uh--
他们还在那儿吗?
舔一下冰棍
你打电话来是取行李的吧?
等等 什么?
Wait, what?
他们落下东西了是吗?
他们压根
他们压根就什么也没带
什么?
What?
喂?
Hello?
有没有人看到他们去哪儿了?
没有
No.
好的
Okay. Uh...
摄像头
Cameras.
我可以看看摄像头吗
我不能亲自去
I can't go in person.
会覆盖了
监控是会覆盖的
The footage overwrites.
多久覆盖一次?
四十八小时
好的
Okay. Uh--
谢谢
Gracias.
希思·达莫尔
是的 女士 没有人知道他们去了哪里
Yes, ma'am. And no one knows where they went.
我明白 是 谢谢
I understand. Yes. Thank you.
大使馆有做点什么吗?
So is the embassy doing something?
不 大使馆下班了 那是当值警官
No, they're already closed. That was a duty officer.
她让我填写一份报告 大使馆明天开的时候就会有人联络我们
She said to fill out a report, and somebody would call us tomorrow when the embassy opens.
监控呢? 那也来不及了啊?
And what about the footage? Won't that be too late?
我知道
I know.
我再打电话 总归是有全天应答的
I'll make some more calls. Somebody's gotta be open 24/7.
海外失踪人口报告
那么 我把这张表填好…
So I'll just fill out this form and--
别担心
Don't worry.
我明天一早在大使馆开放时过来 好吗?
I'm gonna come by first thing tomorrow morning when the embassy opens, okay?
我们肯定能搞定的
We're gonna figure this out.
好的 是
Okay. Yeah.
谢谢 希思
Thanks, Heather.
这是海外服务办公室的表格
失踪人口报告
报表类型:
出走
自愿失踪的成年人
未知
早安 这是法律专员助理易莱哲·帕克
Good morning. This is Assistant Legal Attach  Elijah Park.
请问你是艾伦小姐吗?
Am I speaking with Ms. Allen?
- 喂?  - 嗨 喂?
Hello?Hi. Hi. Hello?
嗨 这是易莱哲·帕克
Hi. Hi there. This is Elijah Park.
我来自美国驻哥伦比亚大使馆
I'm calling from the U.S. Embassy in Colombia.
我以为你们一小时前就上班了?
I thought you guys opened an hour ago.
抱歉 我那个时候和达莫尔小姐通电话
Sorry, I was on with Ms. Damore.
她说你要和我谈谈有关录像的事?
She mentioned you wanted to speak with me about some footage?
是 监控录像 我都写在报告里了
Yes. The security footage, I put it all in the report...
表格缺少签名
我会看看 我现在处于哥伦比亚
Great, I'll take a look. Now, I'm here in Colombia
所以我会成为你和当地警察之间的联络员
so I'll be acting as liaison between you and local police.
你没有收到我的报告?
Did you not get my report?
我们无法处理你的报告
好像是的
Um... Doesn't appear so.
很好 好 嗯 酒店有监控录像 但会一直覆盖
Great. Okay, well, the hotel has security footage, but it constantly overwrites.
所以我们还有六个小时的时间
So we have about six hours until it's gone
你可以派个专员过去吗?
so can you please send an agent over?
我会尽力而为
I'll do my best.
但是记住
But keep in mind,
哥伦比亚法律专员
联邦调查局 没有管辖权在哥伦比亚调查
the FBI doesn't have jurisdiction to investigate in Colombia.
海外办事处- 联邦调查局
所以 与地方当局合作必须花点时间
So it may take some time while we work with local authorities.
法律专员助理易莱哲·帕克
- 很棒  - 现在 听着
- Great. - Now, listen
对我们更有帮助
what's even more helpful to us
就是有关你母亲的任何信息
is any information you can tell me about your mom.
她失踪之前有没有说或做任何异常的事情?
Did she say or do anything unusual before she went missing?
可能是短信 或者语音邮件
Could be a text, a voicemail.
没有
No, not really.
好的 没事
Okay. That's okay.
有没有进入任何网站 好让我们可以用来进行地理定位?
And do you have access to anything we could use to geolocate?
她的谷歌邮箱 iCloud?
Her Gmail, iCloud?
等等 可能…
Wait. Maybe...
密码
妈妈 两个匹配
Spotify 密码 Ca3sar!06 网飞密码 K3vin!!06
听着 合法访问的账户才可以用来做证据
Now, listen, we can only use evidence from accounts that you have legal access to.
要不然 我们知道的一切都不会作为呈堂证供
Otherwise nothing we learn will be admissible in court.
我想我有一些信息
I think I might have something.
graceallen83 密码错误
拜托
Come on.
显示密码
无法登录
没关系 抱歉 没什么网站可以用
Never mind. Sorry, I don't have anything.
没事 我知道你十八岁
That's okay. Now, I know you're 18
你有没有亲戚可以陪着你?
but do you have relatives that could come stay with you?
没有 只有我和我的妈妈
No. Um... It's just me and my mom.
希思可能会过来看看
Heather is probably gonna stop by.
你会取得监控录像吗?
You are going to get that footage, though, right?
把表格交上来
If you get that form in
我保证有专人会去处理 好吗?
I'll make sure it gets to the right hands. Okay?
我们保持联系
We'll be in touch.
下载
创建签名
发送
零分钟前
四个小时前
我已经签了名 随时联系我 很急
联邦调查局的人还没有回复
我觉得他们够呛来得及去酒店
你可以试试 Live cams?
什么?
他们在《非虚构》最后一集用过这个 哈哈
电子旅游
哥伦比亚卡塔赫纳 Live cams
这个只有大型旅游景点
派一个人过去也不麻烦吧
跑腿兔: 别忘了评价你的清洁工作人员 琼
你需要的时候帮助你 触手可及
输入地址
抱歉 这项任务不在我们的范围内
哥伦比亚跑腿兔
英语
在全世界寻找完美的自由职业服务
跑腿
马可 优秀
专长: 英语流利
交通: 小货车 车子
聘用
四十八美元一个小时
价钱
用了五个小时得到我的炸玉米饼
但是杰维是个好人
哈韦尔 [高性价比]
专长: 清理 电气
交通: 摩托车
八美元一个小时
聘用
Facetime 无法使用
手机没有 Facetime 有没有 Whatsapp?
- WhatsApp  - 下载
嗨 喂?
Hi. Hello?
我想你的声音关掉了
I think your sound is off.
哦 嗨 是 嗨 哈韦尔
Oh, hi. Yes, yes. Hi, Javier.
信号正常吗?
Signal okay now?
信号正常 我需要你…
The signal is great. I need you--
你来自哪里?
You are from where?
我来自洛杉矶 我需要…
I'm from Los Angeles. I need--
好莱坞!
Hollywood!
凡奈斯
Van Nuys.
我需要你去这家酒店 然后取得监控录像
I need you to go to this hotel and ask for their security footage.
我试着找某人
I'm tryna find someone.
我没理解什么叫 「试着找」
I don't understand. "Tryna find."
她失踪了
She's missing.
多久了?
How long?
大约三十六小时
Like 36 hours.
我需要某人在录像还未被覆盖之前
And I need someone to get to the hotel
帮我拿到酒店监控录像
and get the footage before it's erased
那么我们可以看到她 和她的男朋友什么时候离开
so we can see when she and her boyfriend left.
警察会帮着找的吧?
La polic awill not check?
不 他们说他们会尽力 但他们不能直接调查
No. No, I mean, they said they would try, but they can't even investigate directly.
所以 我需要你的帮忙
So I need your help.
抱歉 但是…
Ah, lo siento, pero...
我只是提供服务 清理 电气等等
I'm only services. Cleaning, electric, you know.
拜托 她是我妈妈
Please. Please, it's my mom.
拜托
Please.
你让我想起了我的儿子
You make me think of my son.
从不接受拒绝
Never taking no for an answer.
好的
Okay. Okay.
哦 非常感谢
Oh, man, thank you so much.
哦 琼 有趣的事情
Oh, June. Interesting thing.
你知道你的手机一直都在追踪你?
Did you know that your phones are always tracking you?
是的 我知道
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
但是我没办法进入她的账户
But I can't get into her accounts even if I wanted to.
你有试过她的男朋友的吗?
And did you try his?
什么?
What?
你说她和她的男朋友旅游
You said she's traveling with her boyfriend.
那么 如果你找不到她 或许…
So if you can't find hers, maybe...
对
Right.
我能找到他
I can find him.
铃声 前门动作感应
嘿 维
- Yo. - Hey, Vee.
谢谢你能过来 希思还没露面
Thanks for coming by. Heather never showed up.
当然 这简直太疯狂了
Of course. This is so crazy.
嘿 我想凯撒在啃你的智能手表
Hey, I think Caesar's eating your smartwatch.
什么? 我没有智能手表
What? I don't have a smartwatch.
凯文会不会是用同样密码的人呢?
Anyway, does Kevin give you same-password-for-everything type of vibe?
不好讲
Mm, 50-50.
林凯文- 执行总裁
「就像A- B- C一样简单! 」
感觉大概率会啊 你妈妈怎么会看上他?
Actually, 60-40. Why is your mom dating this guy?
希思认为他帅
Heather thinks he's hot.
她当然喜欢
Of course she does.
所以你要撞他的密码?
So you're trying to get his password?
是
Yeah.
专业网页模板
哦 是 这行得通
Oh, yeah. This will work.
你还记得你在电话里模仿 Postmates 司机吗?
Do you remember that time you impersonated the Postmates driver on the phone?
小子 他不知道
Dude, he had no idea.
好的 我需要你的帮忙
All right. I need your help.
求救
为了恢复密码 我需要一些验证信息
So to recover your password, I'll just have to verify a couple things
首先是生日
starting with date of birth.
生日日期
十一月十号 一九八零年
November 10th, 1980.
很棒 你社保的最后四个号码
Great. And the last four of your social.
我不会在电话里说的
I don't give that out on the phone.
那样的话 你的母亲的姓名
In that case, your mother's maiden name.
家庭关系
陈 陈朱丽亚
Uh-- Chen. Julia Chen.
小学学校的名字
And the name of your elementary school.
工作与教育
小学 没有显示学校
- 我小学学校的名字?  - 是
- The name of my elementary school? - Yup.
居住地点 皮尔兰 德州
皮尔兰 德州小学
蒂尔曼小学 凯尼恩小学
先生?
Uh, sir?
你要完整的名字还是…?
Do you need the full name or...?
什么都行
Honestly, whatever works.
蒂尔曼小学?
Tillman Elementary?
输入你的密码
KevinTheeStal1ion
下一步
欢迎 林凯文
亲爱的 我们登上来了
Oh, sweet, we're in.
书签添加
看看他们去了哪里
Okay. Let's see where they were going.
数据和隐私
地图时间轴
星期五 六月十日
优步到洛杉矶国际机场
There's their Uber to LAX.
星期六 六月十一日
飞往卡塔赫纳的航班
Flight to Cartagena.
波马罗莎酒店
酒店
Hotel.
星期日 六月十二日
等等
Wait.
星期日 六月十二日没有位置历史记录
可能他没有信号?
Maybe he didn't have service?
但是他一直发短信给我
But he was texting me the whole time.
除非他关上了他的位置
Unless he turned off his location.
杰维·拉莫斯
WhatsApp
坏消息 录像已经没了
Bad news. The footage is already gone.
但 有个有趣的事
But interesting story.
清洁女工 你们怎么说 清洁太太
La se ora que limpia, how do you say, the cleaning se ora
她和我的儿子一起去学校 然后我们聊了起来…
she went to school with my son. And we got to talking--
不 杰维 没时间听故事了
No, Javi, no time for stories.
等等
Hold on.
那么 我解释给她听我要找的东西
So I explain to her what I'm looking for
而她说她看到两位美国游客星期五离开
and she says she sees two American tourists leave on Friday.
等等 那么 她看到他们离开
Wait, so she saw them leave.
你现在有时间了吧 嗯?
Now you have time for the story, huh?
他们想要离开 而你的妈妈道歉
So they're going to leave, and your mother says sorry
因为她把酒洒在床单上了
because she spilled some wine on the bedsheets.
这大概发生在中午一点钟
This is like 1 in the afternoon.
她穿得很美
She dressed up very nice
清洁太太问 他们是不是去高档场所
so the se oraasked if they were going somewhere fancy.
酒溢出 一点中午离开 盛装打扮
猜猜看你的继父说些什么?
And guess what your stepfather said.
呃 不 不是我的继父
Ew, no, not my stepfather.
哦 好的 但他说他想要去…
Oh, all right. But he says he wants to go to...
怎么说 铁铲铁锤的店…
how do you say, you know, store where shovels and hammers--
等等 五金店?
Wait, a hardware store?
是 五金店
S ,hardware store.
在假期中
On vacation.
他有没有说出店的名字?
Did she say what store they went to?
不 她没问
No, she didn't ask.
肯定有办法解决的
There's gotta be a way to figure it out.
我叫维纳
Yo. Me llamo Veena.
哈啰 你好 我是杰维
Hola. Mucho gusto. Javi.
信用卡记录
Credit card history.
他购买时应该会附加地点
His purchases should have a location attached to them.
登录
选择带有巴士的图片
近期活动
很好 凯文最后的购物
Boom. Kevin's last purchase.
他们失踪的同一天
Same day they went missing.
盖特森马尼 就是那间店
Getsemani. That's the store.
不是 盖特森马尼 那不是店
No. Getsemani. That's not a store.
那是个地区 观光地点
That's an area, muy tur stico
在那里你会花很多钱买饮料
where you go to pay too much for drinks.
盖特森马尼五金店
Okay, well, I'm sending you
我发送给你所有盖特森马尼的五金店
all the hardware stores in Getsemani.
问问员工 看看他们有见到什么吗?
Talk to the workers, see if they saw anything, okay?
或者我去买买口香糖
Or maybe I just buy some gum.Huh?
看看银行单号是否匹配
To see if the bank code matches.
天啊 是 杰维 好的 我现在发送单号给你
Oh, my God. Yes, Javi. Yes. Okay, I'm sending you the code now.
琼 八间店得花点时间 你能接受么?
June, eight stores might take a few hours. Is that okay with you?
剩余资金: $61.24
现在
For now.
我也会看看他的电邮 看看是否有收据
I'll look through his emails too, see if there's a receipt in there.
好的
Okay.
我们开始吧
Here we go, then.
你要检查他的电邮?
You're going through his email?
是 所以?
Yeah, so?So you can't
你不能擅自侵入凯文的电邮
break into Kevin's email without permission.
但是为什么他关上他的位置呢? 那没道理啊
But why would he turn off his locations? That doesn't make sense.
我不知道 你得让警方处理
I don't know, but you need to let the police handle this stuff.
你的监控录像机已经在路上了!
你过来吗?
Um, are you coming over?
抱歉 我要去办公室 我得变更一下客户会议
I'm sorry. I gotta go into the office. I had to change a client meeting.
但是我会过来的
But I'll be there.
照片；）
什么? 是什么?
Whoa.What? What is it?
杰维·拉莫斯
WhatsApp
不好意思 希思 我先挂了昂
Um, sorry, Heather, I gotta go.
没有匹配的 还有六间
No match yet. Six more to go.
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, hold up.
你很完美 我今晚打电话给你；）
我感觉凯文是在脚踏两条船
I- I think Kevin was cheating.
「薄片」?
"Sheeting"?
明显是他的菜
He clearly has a type.
要不检查看看他拉黑的用户?
What if you checked his blocked users?
什么?
His what?
在他的联系人里 还记得《非虚构》外遇的那集?
In his contacts. Remember that one Unfiction episode with the affair?
账号
联系人
拉黑
27位用户被拉黑
这些人是谁呢?
Who are these people?
我的账号被黑了
现在回答我格雷格!
什么鬼?
What the hell?
等等 谁是格雷格?
Wait. Who's Greg?
嘿 怎么了?
Hey, what's going on?
你认真的吗?
达伦 你怎么可以这样? 你理理我
这个女人叫他达伦
This woman calls him Darren.
你偷走了我所有的钱!
你把我账户黑了?
他们要讨回他们的钱
They all want their money back.
大约13,900,000查找结果
一个查找结果
美国联邦地区法院
林凯文 使用别名「赵卢克」
欺诈…注册到「朱格兰汉」
驳回
这家伙不是不忠 他是个…
Dude's not cheating. He's a...
他是个骗子
He's a con man.
东区联邦监狱
三年在东区联邦监狱 去年释放出来
Three years in Eastham Federal Prison. Released last year.
所以你不会是想说我妈妈和重罪犯约会?
So you weren't gonna tell me my mom was dating a felon?
听着 别误会我的意思 我们调查着
Look, don't get me wrong. We are looking into him.
但他从没有和失踪案有关 他用他法定名称
But he's never been involved in a disappearance. And he's been using his legal name.
但你不觉得这也太巧合了吗?
But don't you think this is a pretty big coincidence?
请记住这些案子是在他被判刑之前发生的
Keep in mind that all of these cases were from before his prison sentence.
而且他从未违反假释规定
And he's never violated parole.
好的
Okay.
但那个兔子蛋糕女人呢?  那是今年的
But what about that Bunny Cake girl? That's from this year.
我明白 但现在你是非法侵入林先生的账号
I understand but right now you are illegally accessing Mr. Lin's account.
所有我收到的证据在法庭上是不可受理的
So any evidence that I receive from that gets tossed in court.
都对不上 还剩下三间五金店
谢谢你的帮助
Look, I appreciate the help.
但我们得找到你母亲
But our job is to find your mom
如果构成犯罪 那这才是一个可诉讼的案件
and build a prosecutable case if there's a crime.
所以我们得用合法的方式搜查
So we gotta do this the right way.
这一点你得相信我
You need to trust me on this.
兔子蛋糕310
蕾切尔·佩奇
晚上当调酒师 白天当演员
这一切都是一场梦
今晚来见我 所有酒半价! 八点至十一点晚上
拉奇蒙特试酒间
是 她在这里上班
Uh, yeah, she works here.
你都完全联系不上她了吗?
And you haven't heard from her at all?
没有 我给她打过电话 还发了消息
Nope. I've tried calling, DMing her.
我帮她代班已经两个星期了 所以…
I've been stuck covering her shift for the last two weeks, so...
- 两个星期  - 也不是完全表现反常 她…很特别
- Two weeks. - Not exactly out of character, though. She's... special.
如果有她的消息可以打个电话给我吗? 我很急
Do you mind calling if you hear from her? It's important.
当然
Uh-- Sure.
兔子蛋糕也失踪了 她两个星期没来上班了
Bunny Cake is missing too. She hasn't been to work in two weeks.
你认为他对她做了些什么?
You think he did something to her?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我知道怎么能找到答案
But I know how to find out.
直到他们到了哥伦比亚
Not till they got to Colombia.
拉奇蒙特试酒间
经常到访
他和她有暧昧关系
He wasseeing her.
二十八个地点
大多数到访
你在干什么?
What were you up to?
格蕾丝的家
大通银行
拉奇蒙特试酒间
黄金健身房
那是什么?
What the hell?
驾驶
四百五十五公里
五个小时 十二分钟
48541马里波萨路 山泉水 内华达 私人住宅
地址查询
吉姆W
获取电话
你是怎样得到这个号码的?
And you got this number how?
我联络林凯文 他两个星期前去了你的家
I'm calling about Kevin Lin. He visited your house like two weeks ago.
等等 慢一点 凯文?
Wait, slow down. Kevin?
林凯文 他在你的家…
Kevin Lin. He was at your house...
六月八日 他在那里干嘛?
June 8th. What was he doing there?
听着 我不想透露任何他不想公开的事
Look, I don't wanna say anything that he doesn't want public.
哦 你想要替他隐瞒起来?
Oh, so you're trying to cover for him?
隐瞒什…? 当然不是
Covering for wha--? Of course not.
那么 他怎么会在你的家呢?
Then why was he at your house?
圣父事工 建设人民 而不是监狱
这是为犯罪前科的人准备的重返社会项目
It's a reentry program for ex-offenders.
在我搬到这里之前 我和凯文一组
I was paired with Kevin before I moved out here.
他有的时候会过来拜访
He comes and visits sometimes.
所有的人都应有第二次机会
最难的部分就是让这些人克服污名 那么…
Look, the hardest part for these guys is getting past the stigma, so
我试着谨慎一点
I try to be careful.
是的 太对了
Yeah, totally.
他有没有…
And did he ever...
偶尔提起我的妈妈?
mention my mom anytime?
提起?
Mention?
我是说 他们第一次见面后他一直在谈论她
I mean, he hasn't shut up about her since they first met.
她看起来对他有好的影响
She seemed really good for him.
凯文和我妈妈第一次见面
你记得他们怎么见面的?
Do you remember how they met?
你肯定比我还要清楚
I mean, you'd know better than me.
是的
Yeah.
你不认为这只是他的另一个 你知道吗…
Um, you don't think this was just another one of his, you know...
哦 不 我是说 听着…
Oh, no. I mean, look.
凯文很努力的将那些东西抛在脑后
Kevin's worked really hard to put that stuff behind him.
他很真诚的
It seemed real to me.
是
Yeah.
你说你是吉姆?
And you said your name was Jim?
吉米 是的
Jimmy, yeah.
听着 我会和我的妻子谈谈 看看她是否记得
Listen, I'll talk to the wife. I'll, uh, see if she remembers anything.
吉米教会的人
祝你好运 琼
Good luck, June.
好的 谢谢你 吉米
Okay. Thanks, Jimmy.
是这间店吗?
Is this the store?
你知道我今天买了多少的口香糖呢?
Do you know how many packs of gum I bought today?
有没有人看到他们?
Did anyone see them?
没有人记得
No one remembers.
但是我有收据
But I got the receipt.
等等 你有拿到吗? 他买了什么?
Wait, you got it? What did he buy?
只是这一个
Just this.
是把锁?
A lock?
他为什么要买一把锁?
Why would he buy a lock?
有没有监控录像机?
And what about security cameras?
没有
No.
那么 下一步是什么?
So, what's next?
嘿 我得走了 明天再见
Hey. I gotta bounce. I'll see you tomorrow, though.
好的 是 好吧
Oh. Okay. Yeah, sounds good.
再见 杰维
Hasta luego, Javi.
再见 维纳
Adi s, Veena.
希望我没有浪费你的钱
I hope I didn't waste your money.
没有 杰维
No. No, Javi.
你帮了我很多的忙
You've been really helpful.
你也许该通知警方这把锁的事
Maybe you should tell la polic aabout the lock.
他们也许会知道一些事情
They maybe know something.
当然
Sure thing.
再见 杰维
Peace, Javi.
什么东西?
Piece of what?
不是 是再见
No, like peace.
再见的意思
Just means goodbye.
需要什么的话就发短信给我
Text if you need anything.
搜索附近
旅游景点
凯文和妈妈第一次见面?
艾派迪旅游行程
你有新版本的门票
喜爱的书
嗨格蕾丝! 我想这是 我第一次给你发电子邮件
格蕾丝回复你的信息!
佳人 更好的相遇方式
格蕾丝 43- 凡奈斯 加州
是时候回复她们的信息!
看看信息
在一个合适的地方 面对面聊天和发短信
立即登录
desktraveler11 @gmail.com
成熟的灵魂寻找诚实有趣的人
但希望慢慢来 建立信任对我来说很重要
最好的约会是带我去浪漫的地方
跟我谈谈各种八零年代/九零年代的艺术家
信息
嘿 格蕾丝!
Hey, Grace!
抱歉 我不是故意那么大声说的
Sorry, I didn't mean to say it that loud.
我是凯文
Kevin here.
我只想试着开始认识彼此
And I thought I'd just try to get things started.
谁是你最爱的八零年代乐队?
What's your favorite '80s band?
嘿 格蕾丝! 来看看! 怎么样了啊?
我知道 第三条信息不起作用的
I know, a third message is lame.
但是你很棒 我很想更了解你
But you seem great, and I'd love to know more about you.
还有 哈啰
Also, hello.
我忘了说 好的
I forgot that. Okay.
我很佩服你的坚持 那么 你想了解什么呢?
I certainly admire your persistence. So, what would you like to know?
还在等着你最爱八零年代的乐队
你先开始…
不论你相不相信 想当年 我非常着迷…
Believe it or not, back in the day, I used to be a huge fan of...
New Edition
New Edition.
好的
Okay.
你偷走了我的答案
You totally stole my answer.
我们有百分之九十七匹配度: ）
我是一个一般社交媒媒人
I'm kind of a social media guy clich .
共享办公空间
Shared office space.
从小桶里抽喝啤酒
Uh-- There's beer on tap.
我已经不喝酒了 真的 大概是年纪大了
I don't drink anymore, though, really. Guess I'm gettin' old.
很好 我也不喝酒 不像所有洛杉矶的人都喝
嗨
Hi. Heh.
我正要回家
I'm just getting home.
又是连轴转的一天
Um... Another 13-hour day.
格蕾丝 你应该给自己放个假
You know what, Grace? It sounds like you need a vacation.
远离喧嚣的地方 重新启动
Just get off the grid, do a hard reset.
这对我来说很有效
That's what works for me.
嘿  Siri 我们能来个假期…? 哦 该死
Hey, Siri, can we take a vac--? Oh, crap.
「嘿  Siri 我们能来个假期…? 」
"Hey, Siri, can we take a vaca--?"
不是故意发送的! 抱歉琼
嘿  Siri 提醒我约会格蕾丝吃顿晚餐
Hey, Siri, remind me to ask Grace out to dinner.
等等…
Wait...
在记录着吗?
Is this recording?
猜猜歌曲的名字
Guess what this song is called.
昨晚好开心
Last night was fun.
她还没有回复 我很担心
她肯定只是和朋友出去了
她有没有分享位置?
她应该分享位置 但是不成功!
要我过来吗? 我不想看到你担心
我不知道该做什么
I just don't know what to do.
我试着留言 但她的语音信箱满了
I tried to leave a voicemail. Her voicemail is full.
她关上了定位服务
She turned off location services.
她知道她应该在晚上十一点回来的
And she knows that she's supposed to be home at 11.
她知道这个的
She knows this.
嘿 她快要十八岁了
Hey. She's almost 18.
如果她关上了定位服务
If she took the time to turn off locations
这代表她没事
she's probably okay.
我知道 我只是…
I know, I just...
我不知道
I don't know. She's--
当我看到她时 我…
When I look at her, I just...
我看到了她的爸爸 这好像是…
I just see her father, and it's like...
我们真的在一起经历了很多
We've really been through a lot together.
我不认为我能…
And I just don't think that I could, uh...
万一她有什么意外的话 我不认为我会原谅自己
I don't think that I could forgive myself if anything ever happened to her, you know?
你真是个很棒的母亲
You seem like a really great mom.
有一天 她会懂的
One day, she'll get that.
我希望你是对的
我可以打电话给你吗?
我还要和你谈谈其它的事情
嘿 谢谢你昨晚愿意倾听
我只告诉过另一个人我的过去
只有我们知道这件事 好吗?
当然 我不会告诉别人的
很高兴能够信任你: ）
妈妈的过去往事?
其实 我也有过去保密的经历
So actually, I've got stuff too.
我有前科
I have a record.
我该早一点告诉你的
And I shoulda told you earlier.
但是我真的…
But I just-- I really...
我真的喜欢你 我不想搞砸这件事
I really like you, and I just didn't wanna screw this up.
但是如果你不想要再聊的话
But if you don't wanna keep talking
我完全可以理解的
I totally get it. Um...
那么…
So...
是的
So yeah.
嘿 很抱歉那么长的时间才回复你
我很感激你的诚实 但我有很多的问题
当然 完全理解
如果你想聊的话 我就在你身边
那很好 今天晚些时候有空吗?
当然 随时打电话过来
旅游景点
浪漫旅游景点
马贝拉普拉亚 观光胜地
圣多明各广场 历史地标
圣胡安 观光胜地
寨城爱情锁桥 观光胜地
风景如画的行人桥
寨城爱情锁桥
G- A K- L
"G- A, K- L."
对吗?
S ?
对
Yeah.
就是这个
There it is.
我应该想到这个地方的
I should have thought of this place.
很多游客 也适合情侣来
Lots of tourists. And good for couples.
等一等
Hold on a sec.
哥伦比亚卡塔赫纳 Live cams
这里
There.
爱情锁桥
杰维 你能帮我招手吗?
Javi, can you wave for me?
什么?
Qu ?
招手
Wave.
我看到你了
I see you.
嘿 琼!
Hey, June!
好的 我查一下
Okay, let me check the archive.
六月十九日
快点
Come on, come on, come on.
等等
Wait.
那里!
There!
你看到他们吗?
Do you see them?
是的
Yeah.
他拿着一把锁
He has the lock.
等等
Wait.
等等 他从他的口袋拿出东西来
Wait, he's pulling something out of his pocket.
什么?
What?
这是真的
It was real.
一切都好吗?
Is everything all right?
是的 我过会儿打给你
Um, yeah. Let me call you back.
帕克专员
艾伦小姐? 我们可能找到他们了
Ms. Allen? We may have found them.
我知道他们在桥上 你对
I know they were at the bridge. You were right.
他不是想骗她
He wasn't trying to con her.
- 艾伦小姐  - 是?
- Ms. Allen. - Yeah?
听着
Listen.
我们有坏消息
We've got some bad news.
案件 #1092J 2022- 06- 19 _录像_01
级别: 敏感
天啊
Oh, my God.
这些人是谁?
Who are these people?
我们不知道
We don't know.
我们今早收到匿名消息来源
We just received this this morning from an anonymous source.
我们就在此时派遣执法部门
We're mobilizing units across the city as we speak.
他们要对她做什么?
What are they gonna do to her?
我们确认从你母亲
Well, we flagged a withdrawal
银行账户取款到第三方加密账户的交易
from your mom's bank to an encrypted third-party account
那么 他们可能就是要钱
so they may just want money.
那么 现在怎么办? 我能做些什么吗?
So, what now? Is there anything I can do?
嘿 我们会找出这些人 好吗?
Hey, we're gonna find these guys, okay?
你能做的就是在你的电话旁等着
The best thing you can do to help us is just wait by your phone.
我们再联络
We'll be in touch.
他们说是要钱 但如果这些人伤害了她呢?
They said something about money, but what if these people hurt her?
他们没有理由那样做
They have no reason to.
我已经失去了我的爸爸 杰维 我不能再失去她
I've already lost one parent, Javi. I can't lose her too.
我甚至没有说再见
I didn't even say goodbye.
你什么时候失去你的爸爸?
When did you lose your father?
对不起 如果你不想提起
I- I'm sorry if you don't wanna talk about it.
没事
No, it's fine. Um...
那是几年前的事了
It was years ago.
我甚至不记得他的葬礼了
I can't even remember the funeral.
我的儿子卡洛斯也是很小的时候 失去了他的妈妈
My son Carlos lost his mom when he was very young too.
所以我问你
That's why I ask.
我知道这很不容易
I know it's hard.
是的
Yeah.
你的儿子很幸运 他还有你 杰维
Your son is lucky he still has you, Javi.
我不知道
I don't know.
什么意思呢?
What do you mean?
他一直闹事
He was always trouble.
他的问题变得更糟了 所以有一天我们大吵一番…
But the trouble got worse, then one day we had this big fight and...
他说他永远都不想和我说话
He said he never wanted to talk to me again.
我想他认真的
I guess he meant it.
但是 尽管他不想要见到我
But, you know, even if he doesn't want to see me
他一直都是我的小卡洛斯
he's always mi Carlito.
不管你怎样责怪你的妈妈…
And whatever you are beating yourself over with your mom...
她还是一样的爱着你
it doesn't change a parent's love.
我知道
I know.
你有没有试着联络他?
Have you tried reaching out?
你的儿子
To your son?
他知道我在哪里
He knows where I am.
嗯 不管怎样…
Well, anyway, um...
我不想再浪费你的时间了 杰维
I don't wanna take any more of your time, Javi.
- 谢谢  - 没问题 琼
Thank you.It's no problem, June.
随时打电话给我
Call anytime.
听着 他们一定能找到她
And, listen, they're gonna find her.
我知道
I know.
再见 朋友
Peace, amiga.Hm?
再见
Peace.
欢迎
graceallen83 @gmail.com
和宝贝喝鸡尾酒
无酒精鸡尾酒
酒撒了 一点中午离开
Instagram 蕾切尔·佩奇
晚上当调酒师
白天当演员
照片；）
你很完美 我今晚打电话给你；）
最后一天! 明天在洛杉矶国际机场见!
天啊
Oh, my God.
早安
Good morning.
我是来自美国联邦调查局 易莱哲·帕克
I'm Elijah Park with the FBI.
昨晚我们确定美国公民格蕾丝·艾伦
Last evening we determined that U.S. citizen Grace Allen
之前被认为在哥伦比亚卡塔赫纳被绑架
previously thought to have been kidnapped here in Cartagena, Colombia
实际上是我身后的嫌疑人假冒的
was in fact impersonated in an alleged scheme by the suspects behind me.
我们现在向公众寻求任何
We are now turning to the public for any information
有关艾伦小姐行踪的信息 我们现在相信…
regarding the whereabouts of Miss Allen, who we now believe...
她不曾离开过洛杉矶
never left Los Angeles.
早安洛杉矶
嗨 各位 今早新闻 「我见过最怪异的新闻」
Hi, everybody, first up this morning: "The strangest case I've ever seen."
那些是洛杉矶警局 卢西亚娜·戈麦斯警探说的话
Those are the words used by LAPD Detective Luciana Gomez
来形容凡奈斯失踪的居民
to describe the disappearance of a Van Nuys resident
优步开车到洛杉矶国际机场时
who was seemingly swapped out
似乎被另一位女子换掉了
with another woman along their Uber drive to LAX.
因为是狸猫换太子 我们浪费了很多时间
Because of the staged kidnapping, we've lost a lot of time.
天啊 有人绑架琼的妈妈?
艾伦小姐最后一次出现已超过一个星期
It's now been over a week since Miss Allen was last seen,
那不是琼·艾伦吗?
所以我们要赶紧行动
so we need to move quickly.
今天开始对一名妇女进行地面搜索
A ground search begins today
警方称她在
for a woman police say went missing
前往机场近三十五公里的途中失踪
somewhere along her nearly 22-mile trip to the airport.
格蕾丝!
Grace!
我们在这里
把这个加到你的 Story 里
可以的话 出来支持!  #寻找格蕾丝·艾伦
格蕾丝!
Grace!
前门动作感应
他们跟你聊了一会了 他们都了解了?
They were talking to you for a while. They know anything?
他们认为绑架一定是
They think whatever happened
在开车去洛杉矶国际机场的路上发生的
must have been on the drive to LAX.
对 看看这个 看看他们
Right, right, right. Look at this. Look at 'em.
那么 你的妈妈坐上优步 沿着405
So your mom gets in the Uber, they take the 405
然后 另外一个女子在洛杉矶国际机场走出来
and then a totally different woman gets out at LAX.
如果凯文对她做了什么 事情就在那时候发生
If Kevin did something to her, that's when it happened.
奇怪的是
The weird thing is
一路上他只停了三分钟
he only ever stopped for three minutes along the way.
肯定有帮手
He must have had help.
优步查不到那次行程的记录 车子是套牌
Uber has no record of the trip, and the car was using stolen plates.
我们已经全面通缉那辆车子了
We got an APB out for the vehicle now.
前面这位你说
Yep. Down in front.
有没有可能优步司机是被雇佣的?
Is it possible that the Uber driver was hired?
可能
It's possible.
根据我们美国联邦调查局的朋友…
According to our friends at the FBI...
自从艾伦小姐失踪后
Large withdrawals from Miss Allen's bank account
她账户里一大笔钱被提走
were made after her disappearance.
与此同时 唯一知道这里发生了什么事的人…
In the meantime, the one person who knows for sure what's going on here...
…是林先生
Is Mr. Lin.
所以我们正和当地警方合作
So we're working with the police around the region
这包括委内瑞拉边境的官员
including officers at the Venezuelan border.
我们找到他…
We find him...
我们就能找到格蕾丝·艾伦
And we find Grace Allen.
杰维 他们说了什么?
Javi, what are they saying?
他们说警方逮捕了一些本地学生
They say that the police arrested some local students
他们都是林聘请来演戏的
that Lin hired to be part of a movie.
这是然我上 IMDB 的绝佳机会
然后赚点钱 但是
他甚至都没付我们尾款
琼 看看这个
Whoa. June, check this out.
他们在抓她
They're arresting her. Right now.
就是她 那里
There she is. There, there.
不 你看得到她吗?
No, no, no. Can you see her?
什么?
What?
这不是那个假扮的女孩吗#格蕾丝·艾伦?
有抱负的女演员蕾切尔·佩奇
Aspiring actress Rachel Page
最近在返回美国时被拘留
recently detained upon reentering the U.S.
今天作为合作证人获得保释
was released today on bail as a cooperating witness.
他说这是个真人秀
He said it was a reality show.
像是生活方式旅游
Like a lifestyle travel thing
全都由苹果手机拍摄的
all shot on a iPhone and stuff.
我必须按照特定的方式走路和穿衣
I had to walk a certain way, dress a certain way.
我甚至不能在 Instagram发布内容
And I couldn't even post anything on Instagram.
但是拍摄绑架现场过后
But after the kidnapping scene
我知道一定是出事了
I knew something was up.
所以我逃跑出来
So I made a run for it.
但是没有工作人员没有真正的摄像头
But there was no crew, no real cameras.
这些不是很奇怪吗?
None of that seemed odd?
我在想
I just thought:
「该死 这个男人有远见」
"Damn. This guy has a vision."
蕾切尔·佩奇录像
你怎么知道她不是在说谎呢?
How do you know she's not lying?
佩奇小姐说凯文和他的司机 在靠近405地点接她
Miss Page said Kevin and his driver picked her up near the 405
那么洛杉矶警局检查交通摄像头
so LAPD checked traffic cameras.
正当凯文抵达那里时 你的母亲已经不在了
By the time Kevin got there, your mom was already gone.
佩奇小姐没有见过她
Miss Page never saw her.
好的 嗯 她有没有观察到司机的样子呢?
Okay, well, did she get a good look at the driver?
中年人 棒球帽 我们就只知道这些
Middle-aged, baseball hat, that's all we got.
她在后座看不到他的样子
She couldn't see his face from the back seat.
凯文肯定雇了那个人
Yo, Kevin for sure hired that guy.
维纳 安静
Veena, shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
听着 艾伦小姐 既然我在跟你谈着
Listen, Miss Allen, while I have you
我有几个关于我们正在调查事情的问题
I have some questions regarding something we're looking into.
好的
Okay.
你说你没有重新组建家庭 是吗?
You mentioned that you don't have any extended family, right?
对
No.
据你所知 你母亲从来没有用过别的名字吗?
To the best of your knowledge, your mom has never gone by any other names?
没有 她只有格蕾丝·艾伦的名字 怎么了?
No. She's just Grace Allen. Why?
即时新闻
格蕾丝·艾伦的案件在今晚有独家进展
Exclusive developments tonight in the case of Grace Allen:
公共记录表明失踪的凡奈斯居民
Public records suggesting there may be more
可能比表面看起来的要复杂
to the missing Van Nuys resident than meets the eye.
原来格蕾丝·艾伦只是神秘女人的别名之一
Turns out Grace Allen is just one of the mystery woman's aliases
而她的真实身份隐藏在法院的保密文件之后
whose real identity lies locked behind a court-ordered seal.
你是她的律师 你有什么办法没?
You're her lawyer. There's nothing you can do?
这是法院下达的机密
It's a court-ordered seal.
至少得花上一个星期的时间让法官正式解除
It's gonna take at least a week to get a judge to lift it.
她从来没有对你说过任何东西?
And she never said anything to you about this?
我不…
I don't...
我不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
为什么她要对我隐瞒?
Why would she keep this from me?
这会不会是说格蕾丝·艾伦有同谋关系呢?
Does this suggest Grace Allen herself might be implicated?
我要声明一下
Let me be clear:
到目前为止格蕾丝·艾伦并不是嫌疑人
Right now, Grace Allen is not a suspect.
话虽如此 我们不能排除任何可能性
That being said, we can't rule anything out.
警方「不能排除任何可能性」
格蕾丝·艾伦隐藏些什么?
嗨 你是琼·艾伦吗?
Hi, is this June Allen?
我是网飞公司行政人员 我们想和你谈谈
I'm an executive at Netflix, and we'd love to talk to you.
…打电话来是想问能不能参加我在 Spotify 的播客…
…calling in for my podcast on Spotify--
我留个言试试 我想写一篇关于本次事件的文章…
I tried leaving a voicemail. I'm writing an article--
我是安杰尔 只是问问你妈妈的情况
Yo, it's Angel. Just checking in on things with your mom.
你有没有找到我的手表?
Also, did you find my watch?
消失的钱没有被偷
So the missing money wasn't stolen.
那是支付凯文帮她消失的钱 不然她为什么…
It was payment to Kevin for helping her disappear. Why else would she--
她雇了林和司机 自导自演一场绑架
She hired Lin and the driver, stages the kidnapping
藏在后备箱里 开车走 然后在某个地方开始新生活
hides in the trunk, drives off, starts a new life somewhere.
我们知道她以前做过一次
Which we know she's done once before.
我是说 除了女儿 没有已知的家庭成员?
I mean, zero known family members, other than the daughter?
那是非常可疑的
That's hella sus.
我再也受不了这个了!
I cannot take this anymore!
这只是互联网 琼
It's just the Internet, June.
不 这不仅仅是互联网 警方也一样
No, no, it's not just the Internet. It's the police too.
嘿 一切都会没事的 琼
Hey, hey, hey. It's going to be okay, June.
别让他们困扰你
Don't let them put you down.
这完全没有道理
评论
- 举报推文  - 举报帖子
- 举报  - 假消息
你简直是在瞎编
回复
我们浪费了多少纳税人的钱
How many tax dollars have been wasted
在找一个明显逃跑的人?
searching for someone who clearly ran away?
她的同事说她提及自己的过往就岔开话题
I mean, her coworker described her as dodgy and guarded about her past.
他们怎么能相信这呢?  他们都信错人了
How can people believe any of this? They're focusing on the wrong person.
至少他们试着帮忙
At least they're trying to help.
试着想象这是《非虚构》里的一集
Like, imagine if this was an Unfictionepisode.
你也会提出问题 对不?
You'd be asking questions too, no?
关于凯文 不是我妈妈
About Kevin. Not my mom.
是 但是你也说她隐瞒事实 对不?
Yeah, but even you said she was hiding something, right?
她一直都了解凯文 加上整个身份的改变…
She knew about Kevin the whole time. Plus the whole identity change--
维纳 怎么了?
Veena, what the hell?
不 我是说有一些合乎情理的问题
No, I just mean that there are some legit questions.
根本就没问题!
There are no questions!
这不是一场秀 这是我妈妈!
This is not a show, this is my mom!
琼 显然我…
June, obviously I--
你该离开
You should just go.
铃声 前门动作感应
为什么我们对格蕾丝·艾伦一无所知?
工作与教育
居住地点
家庭关系
没有显示工作地点 没有显示学校
没有显示地方
没有显示关系
没有显示家庭成员
格蕾丝·艾伦调查
格蕾丝·艾伦的卷入
头条新闻: 当局正在调查失踪女子的过去
格蕾丝·艾伦会不会是自己上演失踪事件?
格蕾丝·艾伦的男朋友帮忙隐瞒她的过去?
历史 我的活动
我的谷歌活动
转换身份
已访问 为你的品牌开发数码身份
格蕾丝·艾伦法庭印鉴
无搜索结果
格蕾丝·艾伦计划
如何假装失踪
无搜索结果
如何隐藏身份
如何隐藏互联网历
如何隐藏互联网
访问吉斯加密信使 免费下载
安全地说话
使用端到端加密保护隐私
将消息设置成指定时间后删除
下载
电子邮件: desktraveler11 @gmail.com
登录
无效密码 请重试
忘记密码?
密码重设
密码:
晚上好 kevin.lin80
newuser12419
十个小时前
#11- 21952 两天前
最后二十四小时没有信息
昨天
你告诉琼什么了?
我保证我什么都没跟她说
她还什么都不知道
至: newuser12419
id: newuser12419
大概一个星期前加入
发送加密信息…
谁…
你在家吗?
newuser12419正在打字…
还在工作 有事吗?
我弄丢了
我得买个新的手机
你的号码是
我们必须谈谈
newuser12419正在打字…
你已从其它设备登出
电话号码查询 群众追逐
帕克探员
信息
我是安杰尔…看到我得手表告诉我一下
智能手表带高清摄像头
一天之内她还给凯文发过短信
She was messaging Kevin less than 24 hours ago.
加上自从他们失踪之后 她一直不理我
Plus she's been ignoring me since they went missing.
呼吸 深呼吸 也许有一个好的答案
Breathe. Just breathe. Maybe there is a good answer.
她自从遇见凯文之后就对他着迷 这一切都说得通
And she's been obsessed with Kevin ever since they met. It's all making sense.
- 那是什么?  - 有摄像头
What is that?It has a camera.
这样的话 她不会知道我在录视频
This way, she won't know I'm recording.
琼 如果你觉得有问题的话 你得报警
June, if you think something is wrong you need to tell la polic a.
我试过告诉他们有关凯文和蕾切尔的事
I have tried! I have tried telling them about Kevin and about Rachel.
但我在凯文的账号上找到的任何东西不能作证
But anything I find on Kevin's account can't be used
来协助「建立可起诉的案件」什么的
to help "build a prosecutable case" or whatever
所以我得拍下她
so I have to record her.
我现在要跟手表同步一下
I'm syncing to the watch now.
如果我出事了
I need you to stay on the phone while I'm in there
我需要你不要挂断
in case something happens.
琼 抱歉
June, I'm sorry.
设备连接
这样太危险了
It's too dangerous.
不 警察像是认为我妈妈是幕后主使
No, the police are acting like my mom's some kind of criminal mastermind.
但现在你需要相信他们
Pero maybe right now you need to trust them.
你在说些什么?
What are you saying?
虽然他们是你的父母双亲
Just because someone is your parent
但这不代表他们不会犯错
it doesn't mean they do not make mistakes.
我猜你应该明白
I guess you would know, huh?
或许你对你儿子已经不抱希望了
Maybe you gave up on your son...
但是我从未放弃寻找我妈妈
but I'm not giving up on my mom.
检查周围环境是否安全
琼的苹果手机
摄像头
六月二十七日 晚上十点
It's June 27th, 10 p.m.
在希思·达莫尔的办公室 73815维尔雪大道
at the office of Heather Damore, 73815 Wilshire Boulevard.
快到她办公室了
Approaching her office now.
希思·达莫尔律师事务所
希思?
Heather?
希思 是琼!
Heather, it's June!
希思 我看到你的车子在外面 我知道你…
Heather, I saw your car out there. I know you're--
有人吗?
Hello?
搞什么鬼?
The hell?
清除本地磁盘百分之八十八
你说 她就会死
什么?
What?
有人吗?
Hello?
希思?
Heather?
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊! 希思!
Oh, my God! Heather!
根据尸检结果
Based on the autopsy,
凶手走了没几分钟你就到了
whoever did this was there minutes before you arrived.
你应该庆幸你还活着
You're lucky to be alive.
他们一定是看到了我发送给她的信息
They must've seen the messages I sent to her.
他们知道我会来
They knew I was coming.
我只是不明白为什么她要给他发信息
I just don't understand why she'd be messaging him.
电脑格式化 文件也没了…
Look, the wiped computer, the missing files...
我猜想她知道一些凯文不想要我们知道的事
My guess is that she knew something that Kevin didn't want us to know.
她并不是故意给他发信息
She wasn't willfully messaging him.
他威胁她
He was threatening her.
而照片…
And the photos were...?
为了让她保持沉默
To keep her quiet. Yeah.
她试着保护我
She was trying to protect me.
但如果凯文还在哥伦比亚的话 那么是谁做的?
But if Kevin is still in Colombia, who did this?
我不知道
I don't know.
但与此同时 洛杉矶警局会保护你
But in the meantime, LAPD will stay there with you
直到给你找到安全的住处 好吗?
until they find a safe place for you to go. Okay?
林先生是这所有事情的关键人
Look, Mr. Lin is the key to all of this.
好消息是 警方可能在边境附近发现了他
Now, the good news is police may have spotted him near the border,
所以 事情不会拖得太久的
so it might not be long.
他是我们找到你母亲最好的机会
He is our best chance at finding your mom.
是
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
头条新闻: 失踪女子的朋友遭人谋杀
警方说受害者被勒索
格蕾丝·艾伦的记录消失不见
琼苹果笔记本电脑
CyberGhostVPN 连接到: 美国#5923
遥控器
琼苹果笔记本电脑 HP Spectre_JW 星期二
琼苹果笔记本电脑 HP Spectre_JW 星期一
琼苹果手机 HP Spectre_JW 星期一
琼苹果笔记本电脑 HP Spectre_JW 星期日
新闻里到处都是我
别轻举妄动 我要回去看看琼
他们知道我在哪里 我找人帮我离开哥伦比亚
我已经给你钱了
kevin.lin80 正在打字…
拜托 你不能把我丢在这里
这一切都是我计划的
没有人会怀疑你
你没有我的话 不可能办得到
拜托 我不能回监狱
维纳 他们找到他了
壹巡查 实时报道犯罪
警方正在进行突袭绑架嫌疑人
所有人都在看
里面有任何动静吗?
我们走吧
希望他们打死他
警察!
! Polic a!
好的! 嘿! 等等!
Okay! Hey! Hold up!
冷静
Tranquilo.
我不明白
No comprendo.
拜托!
Please!
原始视频: 美国逃亡者在哥伦比亚边境被杀
嫌疑犯试图带着钱逃跑 这些钱是从失踪女子处盗取的
主要嫌疑犯的死 让格蕾丝·艾伦的案子没有线索了
你还好吗?
还好 在有安全的地方住之前警察都在这里守着
要不要来我这边? 你要住多久就多久
行 他们说可以
好的 警察要走了 我去你那边
前门动作感应
三年电信欺诈 逃税 东汉姆联邦监狱
关机…
你确定你现在要关闭你的电脑吗?
关机
妈妈 你在哪里?
取消
妈妈 如果你看到的话 我保证我们会找到你的
一有信号就给我打电话 我开始担心了
哈啰?  我想我得回去了?
爱你
清除你的语音信箱 我好给你留言!
二十八个语音邮件
妈妈7/6/22 妈妈5/6/22
妈妈27/5/22 妈妈23/5/22
嘿 亲爱的 这是妈妈
Hey, sweetheart. It's Mom.
妈妈想问你今晚要不要看戏…
Just, um, wondering if you wanted to catch a movie toni--
嗨 我是格蕾丝·艾伦
Hi, my name is Grace Allen, and
我其实是你妈妈
I'm actually your mother
方便的时候尽早给我回电话
if you could call me back at your earliest convenience.
嘿  Siri 联络琼…
Hey, Siri. Call Junie--
哦 天啊 抱歉 我以为这是…
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry. I thought this was a--
没关系
Never mind.
嘿 小甲虫
Hey, Junebug.
这是妈妈
It's Mommy.
妈妈敲门来着 但你没应
I tried knocking, uh, but you didn't answer.
你肯定戴着耳机吧
I'm sure you have your headphones on.
实际上呢 妈妈有很多想跟你谈的事
Look, there's actually a lot I want to talk with you about.
你甚至有可能没听这些信息
So anyway, you're probably not even checking these messages
但是我们待会儿再聊
but I guess we'll talk later.
妈妈爱你
I love you.
再见…
Bye--
嘿 小甲虫 这是…
Hey, Junebug. It's--
登录 graceallen83
密码
欢迎 格蕾丝·艾伦
数据和隐私
地图时间轴
星期五 六月十日 2022年
洛杉矶国际机场
位置数据丢失
谷歌和你的手机失去了联系
人员和分享
一位用户被拉黑
阻止交流
- 找到你「格蕾丝」  - 一年前
她有权知道
搜索邮件
你的监控录像机已经在路上了!
9x监控录像机 订阅埃尔斯特一年
订单汇总 1x高级保安套装
用户名是我的邮箱 我会在电话里告诉你密码
登录
登录管理你的设备
忘记你的密码?
重置密码
重置
摄像头
工具室 活跃
查看
工具室直播
有人吗?
Hello?
走廊
侧边_庭院_1
还未命名的设备
琼的文档
最后一次家庭旅行
吉米 教会的人
- 哈啰?  - 琼?
- Hello? - June?
感恩 你没事吧?
Thank God. Are you safe?
没事 我想是吧 怎么了?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Why?
所有的门都锁上了吗?
Are all the doors locked?
是的 是吧
Yeah, I think so.
等等 你是教会的吉米吗?
Wait, this is Jimmy from the church thing?
听着 有太多要解释了 但我们不知道谁听着
Look, there's a lot to explain, but we don't know who's listening.
好的 我该叫人来吗?
Okay. Well, should I call someone?
不 我不知道这个时候该信任谁
No, no, no, I don't know who to trust at this point.
听着 别挂电话 好吗?
Look, just stay on the phone with me, okay?
天啊 有人来了
My God. Someone's here.
是我
It's just me.
别担心 一切都没事的
Don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
什么?
What?
你在这里干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我用最快的速度赶来的 我不是要吓坏你的
I came as soon as I could. I didn't mean to scare you.
不 我还未报警之前 你得告诉我发生了什么事
No, you need to tell me what's going on right now before I call the police!
听着
Listen.
我知道这听起来荒谬
I know this sounds crazy.
我尽可能赶过来的
I came as soon as I could.
很抱歉这样子出现…
I'm sorry to show up like this...
但是有些事情…
but there are things...
但是有些事情你该知道
There are things that you need to know.
我可以解释这一切
I can explain everything.
琼?
June?
你还在那里吗?
Are you still there?
琼
June.
琼?
June?
如果你听见的话…
If you can hear me...
听着 我知道这很不容易
Look, I know this is hard.
但是你有权知道发生了什么事
But you deserve to know what happened.
拜托
Please.
琼?
June?
爸爸
Dad.
琼
June.
等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
好的
Okay, okay.
等等
Wait.
好的
Okay.
发生了什么事?
What is going on?
你的妈妈…
Your mom...
她真正的名字是莎拉
Her real name is Sarah.
当你还小的时候
And when you were little
我们一直吵架
we were always fighting.
她都不让我喂你吃东西…
She barely would let me feed you...
也不让你跟你一起玩耍
or play with you.
每一天都变得越来越糟糕
Every day it got worse and worse.
直到她把你带走
Until she took you away.
我从那个时候开始就一直找你
And I've been searching for you ever since.
嘿
Hey.
凯撒
Caesar.
她告诉我你已经死了
She told me you were dead.
琼 你不知道她能做出什么事来
June, you don't know what she's capable of.
她对法官撒谎让我坐牢
She lied to a judge to have me put in prison
这样她就能霸占你
so that she could have you to herself.
她对我撒谎
She lied to me.
十二年来的每一天…
Every day for 12 years...
我每每在东汉姆醒来 也不知道她把你藏在什么地方了
I had to wake up in Eastham knowing that she had you somewhere.
你在东汉姆监狱?
You were in Eastham Prison?
在德州?
In Texas?
琼
June.
她夺走了我所有的一切
She took everything from me.
但凯文就在那里
But that's where Kevin was.
你不是他的咨询师
You weren't his counselor.
你们在监狱里就认识了
You met him in prison.
优步司机?
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
拜托
Please.
琼
June.
我们能谈一会儿吗?
Can we just talk for a minute?
她在哪里?
Where is she?
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
- 嘿 不! 琼!  - 救命!
Hey, no! June!Help!
不!
No, no, no!
拒绝
没事的
It's okay.
铃声 前门动作感应
维纳 未接电话
那么 爸爸会再修好的 对吗?
Well, then I'm just gonna fix it again, aren't I?
那是什么?
What's that?
- 詹姆斯  - 海拔太高了
- James. - It's just the altitude.
- 我没事  - 詹姆斯 你没事吧?
- I'm fine. - James, are you okay?
不 爸爸没事
No, no, no, no. Daddy's fine.
詹姆斯
James.
你没事吧?
Are you good?
嘿 你要不要玩躲猫猫?
Hey, do you wanna play hide-and-seek? Mm-hm.
你要上楼吗? 我数到二十
Okay. You wanna go upstairs? I'll count to 20.
别让爸爸找到你 好吗?
And don't let Daddy find you. Okay?
- 你干嘛要在她的面前那样做?  - 做什么?
- Why you gotta do that in front of her? - Do what?
「你没事吧? 」
"Are you good?"
我现在不能和我的女儿一起玩吗?
What, I can't play with my own daughter now?
- 我什么也没说  - 真的吗?
- I didn't say anything. - Seriously?
只是我看到你从后面出去了 而我知道…
It's just that I saw you go out back and I know--
你录着吗?
Are you filming this?
- 不 我没录任何东西  - 给我摄像头
- No, I'm not filming anything. - Give me the camera.
拨出电话…詹姆斯
莎拉 我给你打电话来着 你在哪里?
Sarah, I've been trying to call. Where are you?
你在家里吗?
Are you at the house?
是的
Yeah.
听着 不如你和琼回来 然后我们谈一谈
Look, how about you and June come back and we talk this out. Okay?
如何利用化妆来掩饰瘀伤
你答应过我不会再次吸毒的
You promised me you would stay clean.
什么? 你以为我吸毒?
And what, you're saying I haven't?
十个危险信号的关系 如何离开虐待你的伴侣
你不能编故事来偷走我的女儿 莎拉
You can't just make shit up in order to steal my daughter from me, Sarah.
来自: 詹姆斯 莎拉回答我
我需要你 宝贝
听着 亲爱的莎拉 对不起
Look, Sare-bear, I'm sorry.
我不是故意生气的
I didn't mean to get upset.
举报虐待
当你不承认事实时
It's just-- It is frustrating trying to reason with you
跟你讲道理让人不愉快
when you won't acknowledge baseline facts.
什么事
德州虐待判决指南
一年以下刑期
你怎么了?
听着 我保证我没有吸毒
Look, I promise I'm clean.
浏览记录
你可以回家吗
Can you just come home
那么我们才能像一家人一样解决问题?
so that we can work this out as a family?
你永远不会离开我
为了琼的好?
For June's sake?
开始无痕浏览
历史记录不会被保存
那么 你怎么解释 我在走廊的壁橱里找到的东西?
Then how do you explain what I found in the hallway closet?
什么?
What?
服刑时间
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
因持有毒品而被判入狱的时间
我们来躲猫猫
We were playing hide-and-seek.
毒品 十至二十年
猜猜看琼找到了什么
And guess what June found.
好的 莎拉 是 我有方法收购和出售毒品
Okay, Sarah. Yes, I found a way to turn some stuff over,
能赚很多 所以你少废话
but it's worth a lot so you need to cut the shit
告诉我你做过了什么!
and tell me what you did with it!
报案
我把它放在原来的地方
I left it where it was.
警察! 打开门!
Police! Open the door!
天啊 你干了什么?
Jesus Christ, what did you do?
我不能让你将我们的女儿置于危险之中
I can't let you put our daughter in danger anymore.
你必须打开门!
You need to open the door!
我发誓 我会找到你…
I swear to God, I will find you
录制中
…在你把她从我身边夺走之前
and you will die in a pool of your own blood
你会倒在血泊之中死去!
before you take her from me!
你听到吗?
Do you hear me?!
结束通话
圣安东尼奥居民被判十年
詹姆斯·沃克被控袭击 私藏毒品
电话_录音.MP3
附加录音
我会找到你和
发送
身份保护资料
我是你的联络人
请仔细附上指南
为了公益帮助你
因为我不是执法人员
致敬 希思·达莫尔
家庭暴力与家庭法
保护令
居家安全 招募计划
保密身份更改指南
你必须停用之前的所有账号
包括所有个人、财务和法律账号
删除谷歌账号
删除我的账号
你必须与所有联系人断绝联系
I can't imagine what you must be going through.
我们真的不想你离开
We really hate to see you go.
我无法想象你得经历的一切
I really had no idea what you were going through.
我爱你 我在为你和琼祈祷
I love you. I'm praying for you and June.
你必须撒谎来保密
I know you two are gonna get through this together.
我们会想念你的
Just-- We're gonna miss you a lot.
有一天她会明白的
Someday she'll understand.
不!
No!
剪裁
给琼
后院_二
走廊
不!
No! No!
我要去处理一件事 然后我们离开
Just gotta take care of one thing, and then we'll leave.
后院_二
工具室
天啊
Shit.
我们出去外面
We're going outside.
如果你要杀我 你早就做到了
If you were gonna kill me, you woulda done it already.
事情有所改变
Things have changed.
琼
June.
琼!
June!
十二年 莎拉
Twelve years, Sarah.
十二年 我当时的感觉就像你现在的感觉
Twelve years, I felt just like you feel right now.
我希望我能把关在这里 但是…
I wish I could've kept you here. But...
我和琼必须离开
June and I have to go.
琼!
June!
天啊 琼!
Oh, my God. Junie!
- 妈妈! 妈妈?  - 没事 宝贝 你没事
- Mom! Mom? Mom? - Okay, baby. You're okay.
- 真的是你吗?  - 宝贝 我很抱歉
- Is that really you? - Baby, I am so sorry.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我们必须逃离这里 明白吗?  他情绪和精神不定
We have to get out of here, do you understand me? He is spiraling.
- 他杀死了希思  - 他杀死了希思?
- He killed Heather. - He killed Heather?
他疯了 他认为他现在是在报复我
He's crazy. He thinks he's punishing me for what I did to him.
好的 在车上我再好好的告诉你
Okay. I'm gonna tell you everything in the car.
我要你拿着锁匙…
I want you to take the keys--
不 妈妈!
No, Mom!
不!
No! No! No, no, no!
天啊!
Oh, my God!
天啊
Oh, God.
他去了哪里?
Where is he going?
椅子
The chair.
- 他要对我们做什么?  - 我不知道
- What is he gonna do to us? - I don't know.
我甚至不知道他为什么带你过来
I don't even know why he brought you here.
因为他知道了
Oh, 'cause he knew.
他知道我会找到他
He knew I was about to find him.
等等
Wait.
低电量 你的苹果笔记本电脑快进入睡眠状态
哈啰? 有人听见吗?
Hello? Hello, hello? Can anyone hear me?
好的 琼 我们必须趁他不在的时候离开
Okay, June, we have to get out of here while he's still outside.
你的电话呢?
Where's your phone?
我没带上电话 在家里 要是我能…
I don't have my phone. It's at the house. If only I could just...
天啊
Oh, my God.
什么?
What?
天啊 对!
Oh, my God, yes!
你还记得这个地方的地址吗?
Do you remember the address to this place?
大概是马里波萨路?
I think it was something Mariposa Road?
但是我就只记得这些
But that's all I remember.
所有东西都需要配上手机
Everything needs to be paired with a phone.
等等
Oh, gosh.Wait.
除非…
What?Unless...
设置
无线网络开启 选择网络
詹姆斯电话 不安全的网络
好的 我有个办法
Okay. I have an idea.
琼 好莱坞
我需要看导航 请别再打来了 好吗? 再见
I need to use the navigation. Please do not call again. Okay? Bye.
杰维 拜托! 我很抱歉我所说的话
Javi, please! I'm sorry about what I said.
你没有放弃你的儿子
You did not give up on your son.
我找到了我的妈妈 但我们没有时间了
I found my mom, but we're running out of time.
拜托 我需要你的帮忙
Please, I need your help.
拜托
Please.
什么?
What?
我需要你登录 我的 Instagram然后找照片
I need you to go to my Instagram and find a picture.
他还没来 拜托快一点
I still don't see him.Javi, please hurry.
是 等等
S , s , momentico.
账号名称是什么?
What's the account name?
是J- U- 下面划线- U...
It's J- U-underscore- U--
「下面划线」? 什么东西?
"Underscore"? Qu  es eso?What's that?
这是一条小线 在下面
It's the little line, like at the bottom, you know?
是
Yeah.
那么 是J- U- 下面划线- U- N- E- 1
So it's J- U-underscore- U- N- E-1.
好的 你去找我 Instagram 第一张照片
Okay, I need you to go to the first picture on my Instagram.
很棒 我们家的后面有号码 是什么?
Great. On the house behind us, there are numbers. What are they?
四八五四一
48541.
好的 报警告诉警方我们在4…
Okay, call the police and tell them we are at 4--
天啊
Oh, no.
他回来了
He's coming back.
退后
Get back.
怎么了?
What's going on?
给我手表
Give me the watch.
嘿!
Hey!
我和我的女儿说话
I am talking to my daughter.
琼 你刚刚打过电话吗?
June, did you just make a call?
好的 现在 我要你跟着我
Okay. Now, I need you to come with me right now.
退后
- James. - Back off.
- 琼 跟着我 拜托  - 放过她
- June, come with me, please. - Leave her alone.
你再说一句话 我就杀了你
One more word from you, and you are dead.
琼 我不想再重复了
June, I'm not gonna ask again.
拜托别…
Please don't--
妈妈!
Mom!
不!
No, no, no!
妈妈!
Mom!
你做了什么? 不!
What did you do?! No!
你做了什么?
What did you do?
琼…
June--
来吧 嘿!
Come on. Hey!
放开我!
Get off of me!
瞧? 没事
See? It's okay.
你只会让事情变得更难
You're just making this harder.
拜托
Please.
不!
No, no, no!
嘿! 放开我们!
Hey! Hey, let us out! Let us out!
妈妈!
Mom!
妈妈
Mom. Mom.
不
No.
爸爸 拜托 请别那样做
Dad. Dad, please. Please don't do this.
拜托 如果你听到我说话 开门 拜托!
Please, if you can hear me, just open the door, please!
她需要帮忙! 拜托!
She needs help! Please!
没必要死人的 打求助电话吧!
No one has to die. Just please call for help!
任何人!
Anyone!
如果任何人听到我说话
If anyone can hear me
我和我妈妈被困在房间里!
I am trapped in a room with my mom!
我们在马里波萨路48541
We are at 48541 Mariposa Road.
附近的医院
任何人
Anyone.
小甲虫?
Junebug?
妈妈
Mom.
不 妈妈 没事的
No. Mom, it's okay.
天啊
Oh, my God.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不
No, no, no.
不 不要那样说
No, you don't say that. No. No, you don't say that.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我保证…
I promise...
我保证如果我们能回家 我会很听话的
I promise if we could just get home, I'll be better.
我会开始检查我的语音信箱
I'll start checking my voicemails.
尽管叫我小甲虫
I'll let you call me Junebug all you want.
我不会再嘲笑你几乎所有的东西都用 Siri
And I'll stop making fun of you for using Siri for literally everything.
我只是…
I just...
嘿  Siri
Hey, Siri.
拨打911
Call 911.
马里波萨路48541求救呼号
Distress call at 48541 Mariposa Road.
附近所有可调遣的小组 马上报到
Any available units in the vicinity, report immediately.
进去!
Go, go, go!
- 进去!  - 安全!
- Go, go, go! - Clear!
- Go, go, go! - Clear.
检查另一边!
Check the other side!
走廊安全
Hallway clear.
嫌疑犯受伤了!
Suspect down!
救命!
Help!
我们需要帮忙!
We need help!
- SWAT! 让我看到你的手!  - 举手!
- SWAT! Let me see your hands! - Hands up!
受害者受伤!
Victim down, victim down!
安全!
Clear!
肺部受伤 我们需要现在给她运走
Lung's collapsed. We need a transport now.
她没事吧?
Is she okay?
30小组联系管制区 有个成年女性
30- Squad to Control, we have an adult female
上身中枪 要求空运
upper body GSW, requesting airlift.
小甲虫?
你在那里吗?
你在观赏《非虚构》第三季
绑架格蕾丝·艾伦: 第九集
只想打个招呼
是
刚刚看完一集
为什么大家都喜欢这种垃圾
好看不?
什么?
你准备好明天 我的天啊 Siri
打电话吧
妈妈  Facetime
接受
妈妈 连接…
嘿 小甲虫 是妈妈 希望我没有打扰到你…
Hey, Junebug, it's Mom. I hope I'm not interrupting--
- 妈妈?  - 是的?
- Mom? - Yeah?
这是 Facetime
This is FaceTime.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
我知道 我只是放下来一会儿
I know, I know. I just put the phone down for a second.
我只想要提醒你 巴士早上八点三十五分离开
Mm-hm.I just wanted to remind you that your bus leaves at 8:35 in the morning
所以你得多设置几个闹钟
so you might wanna set multiple alarms.
是 我设置了
Yep. Already did.
如果你需要的话我也可以给你点午餐零花钱 好吗?
I'll also send you some lunch money if you need any, okay?
什么?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
谢谢
Just thank you.
哦 猜猜看是什么
Oh, guess what.
你的朋友杰维在面子书上加我为好友
Your friend Javi friended me on Facebook.
真的吗? 不是吧
For real? No way.
- 很棒杰维!  - 再见
他很幸运有你这样的爸爸
好的 我们明天下午在联合车站见吧
Okay. Well, I guess I'll see you at Union Station tomorrow afternoon.
迫不及待了
Can't wait.
再见
Bye.
哦 嘿…
Oh, hey--
抱歉!
别担心 我会取票的
爱你
天啊 不是吧?
妈妈也爱你 小甲虫
迫不及待想见你
谜踪搜救